Diana Gureev

Full stack engineer

Tel-Aviv | 058-6558875 | dianagureev@gmail.com

Github | LinkedIn | Portfolio | Medium.com

SUMMARY

Experienced Full stack Developer in both frontend and backend development. Proficiency in Python OOP, React, Node.js, SQL databases and AWS cloud technologies. Background in project management for SaaS brings me excellent communication skills, ability to learn and work fast and strong "get things done" approach.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Node.js, React, Python, SQL, AWS, Git/GitHub, Figma, Jira

PROJECTS

PRISET (Django, React, PostgreSQL, Matplot, Plotly) - Github | Demo

 The analytics platform for monitoring global energy rules and rewards, helping energy industry players understand changes, achieve green goals, and benefit from new opportunities and innovation. Code on the server-side is confidential under an NDA.

SelfishTLV (Node.js, React, Python, PostgreSQL, Google Map API) - Github | Demo

Self-guided tours in Tel-Aviv for new olims with a predefined route on interactive Google map.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

Tel-Aviv, Israel

PRISET (analytics platform)

Mar, 2024 - present

- Develop a full stack app with React, Django server and PostgreSQL database.
- Work with Matplotlib, Plotly, Pandas, Numpy Python libraries.
- Collaborate with remote teams and freelance developers.

Full Stack Developer

Tel-Aviv. Israel

Jan, 2024 - present

Cyber Security
Develop Full Stack app on Ruby on Rails with PostgreSQL provided clean and efficient code.

- Integrate the AWS S3, Lightsails, EC2, Lambda services.
- Develop and deploy RESTful APIs utilizing Python and Node.js.
- Work in a dynamic environment, meeting tight deadlines and collaborating with senior developers to deliver high quality solutions.

Project manager

Saint-Petersburg, Russia

Topvisor (SaaS startup)

2021 - 2023

- Managed the successful launch of the course tailored for SEO professionals, focusing on the technical aspects of website development.
- Conducted analysis of Google Search algorithms and documentation.
- Built prototypes in Figma, HTML/CSS and Python for use by design and R&D teams.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development, Python and JavaScript

Developers Institute, Tel-Aviv Coding Bootcamp

Tel-Aviv, Israel

2023

Customer Success

Tel-Aviv, Israel

Jumpln

2023

Bachelor's Degree in Journalism

Belgorod State University

Belgorod, Russia

2012-2015

LANGUAGES

English - Fluent, Hebrew - Working proficiency, Russian - Native